{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Bachelor",
      "answer": "spinster",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["spinster", "cow", "heifer", "filly"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Bull",
      "answer": "cow ",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["cow ", "baffalo", "hen", "sahiwal"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Bullock",
      "answer": "heifer",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["heifer", "cow ", "sahiwal", "gir "]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Cock (Rooster)",
      "answer": "hen",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["hen", "chicken", "bresse", "barnevelder"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Colt",
      "answer": "filly ",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["filly ", "spinster", "heifer", "cow "]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Dog",
      "answer": "bitch",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bitch", "baffalo", "hen", "chicken"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Drake",
      "answer": "duck",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["duck", "hen", "hen", "barnevelder"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Drone",
      "answer": "bee",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bee", "witch", "heifer", "gir "]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Gander",
      "answer": "goose",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["goose", "lady", "bitch", "duck"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Gantleman",
      "answer": "lady",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["lady", "bitch", "bee", "goose"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Monk",
      "answer": "nun",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["nun", "mare", "niece", "witch"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Horse",
      "answer": "mare",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["mare", "nun", "vixen", "niece"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Nephew",
      "answer": "niece",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["niece", "nun", "mare", "vixen"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Wizard",
      "answer": "witch",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["witch", "nun", "niece", "mare"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Fox",
      "answer": "vixen",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["vixen", "witch", "niece", "nun"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Tiger",
      "answer": "tigress",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["tigress", "lioness", "negress", "aunt"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Lion",
      "answer": "lioness",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["lioness", "tigress", "negress", "heroine"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of Negro",
      "answer": "negress",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["negress", "aunt", "nun", "mare"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Uncle",
      "answer": "aunt",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["aunt", "negress", "mistress", "bride"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Hero",
      "answer": "heroine",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["heroine", "mistress", "bride", "hind"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Master",
      "answer": "mistress",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["mistress", "bride", "hind", "madam"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Bride groom",
      "answer": "bride",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bride", "hind", "madam", "daughter"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Stag",
      "answer": "hind",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["hind", "madam", "daughter", "lass"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Sir",
      "answer": "madam",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["madam", "daughter", "lass", "jenny"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Son",
      "answer": "daughter",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["daughter", "lass", "queen", "ewe"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of   Lad",
      "answer": "jenny",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["jenny", "queen", "ewe", "sow"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  jack",
      "answer": "jenny",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["jenny", "queen", "ewe", "sow"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of  Tom",
      "answer": "queen",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["queen", "ewe", "sow", "fiancee"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of   Ram",
      "answer": "ewe",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["ewe", "sow", "fiancee", "queen"]
    },
    {
      "question": " Feminine  gender of   Boar",
      "answer": "sow",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["sow", "ewe", "fiancee", "jenny"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Feminine gender of Fiance",
      "answer": "fiancee",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["fiancee", "ewe", "sow", "lass"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Masculine is to man as-------- is to women.",
      "answer": "feminine",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["feminine", "famine", "female", "famina"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is wrongly paired",
      "answer": "warden  -wardress",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "warden  -wardress",
        "master - mistress",
        "widower - widom",
        "fox - vixen"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of dog is-------",
      "answer": "bitch",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bitch", "colt", "mare", "witch"]
    },
    {
      "question": "change the gender goose",
      "answer": "gander",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["gander", "geese", "geose", "gossen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A male duck is called--------",
      "answer": "drake",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["drake", "duckling", "dude", "duke"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of  bachelor is -----------",
      "answer": "maid",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["maid", "lady", "madam", "singora"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of  gentleman -------",
      "answer": "lady",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["lady", "women", "maid", "gentle woman"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Prince - princess : Duke :-----",
      "answer": "duchess",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["duchess", "dukee", "she duke", "queen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The princess had a beautiful whilte ------ (Horse). fill in the blank with feminine form of word given in the bracket",
      "answer": "mare",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["mare", "bitch", "horses", "vixen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The masculine gender of traitress is ........",
      "answer": "traitor",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["traitor", "bachelor", "spinster", "nun"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine form of master is -----",
      "answer": "mistress",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["mistress", "miss", "mrs", "she- master"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following  pair is wrong.",
      "answer": "duck - dukess",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "duck - dukess",
        "horse - mare",
        "traitor - traitress",
        "lion - lioness"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of milkman is------",
      "answer": "milk maid",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["milk maid", "milk women", "milk lady", "milk  girl"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of lady is -----",
      "answer": "lass",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["lass", "lady", "lazy", "lase"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The feminine gender of nephew is ---- ",
      "answer": "niece",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["niece", "nephrite", "nephritic", "nephritis"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A duke 's wife is knows as--------",
      "answer": "duchess",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["duchess", "queen", "lady duke", "lass"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following words are wrongly paired?",
      "answer": "bull - bully",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "bull - bully",
        "hunder - huntress",
        "bride groom  - bride",
        "sultan - sultana"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Nephew is to niece as bachelor is to------",
      "answer": "spinster",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["spinster", "wife", "widow", "NOT"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the other gender of horse.",
      "answer": "mare",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["mare", "rooster", "mule", "doe"]
    }
  ]
}
